Contact

jjmaze@mac.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jennymaze (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Healthcare

Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support Pediatric Advanced Life Support Basic Life Support

Jenny Maze, RN

COO at Quinsite

Chapel Hill, North Carolina

Summary

With a background in critical care and interventional cardiology/ radiology nursing I bring the benefit of clinical insights and expertise, strong analytical skills, patient focused innovation, and collaborative approach to problem solving. I manage operations, strategic planning, finance, and marketing for Quinsite. I also enjoy volunteering and connecting with the community.

Experience

Quinsite
Chief Operating Officer
April 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months)
Chapel Hill, NC

Quinsite (formerly known as Mile 5 Analytics) offers software as a service (SaaS) and consulting services. We are dedicated to improving decision making through the use of advanced analytics that help to optimize business outcomes. We combine technical expertise with extensive business knowledge. Quinsite streamlines the data collection process, builds analytics around your data, then designs tools that highlight what you want to see in easily understood and visually meaningful reports.

- We optimize business outcomes by enhancing decisions through advanced analytics
- We transform data into user-friendly tools to help drive your business with precision and speed
- We partner with you to deliver customized solutions that meet your individual needs
- Our reporting tools can be accessed anytime, anywhere, on any device

Why settle for a one-size-fits-all approach when you can have custom information that meets your needs, your priorities, your vision. Every organization is unique and our analytic architects will design full service custom solutions to compliment your specific environment. We cover the

entire spectrum by evaluating back-end processes (data identification, storage, processing) to ensure they support front-end applications (dashboards, reports, alerts). When you collaborate with Quinsite, we will work with you to ensure requirements are clearly understood and expectations are met.

St.Vincent Health Registered Nurse 2005 - February 2018 (13 years) Indianapolis, IN

Interventional Radiology / Cardiac Cath Lab

R&G Medical Legal Solutions, LLC Nurse Consultant 2010 - 2012 (2 years)

Medical legal case review

Advanced Cardiac Specialists Registered Nurse 2003 - 2005 (2 years) Mesa. AZ

Cardiac Cath Lab

PeaceHealth
Registered Nurse
July 2001 - August 2003 (2 years 2 months)
Eugene, OR

Interventional Radiology / Cardiac Cath Lab

Medical Express Travel Nurse Registered Nurse 2000 - 2001 (1 year) Critical Care Units (Arizona, Oregon)

Northwest Community Healthcare Registered Nurse January 1999 - July 2000 (1 year 7 months) Arlington Heights, IL

Critical Care Unit

Education

Purdue University BSN, Nursing · (1994 - 1998)